

TESSA CHAN

Graphic Designer

CONTACTS

W | www.tessachandesigns.com

E | tessachan@hotmail.co.uk

M | 07795 196335

EDUCATION

Arts University Bournemouth

September 2015 - June 2018

BA (Hons) Graphic Design

First Degree Honours

Brockenhurst College

September 2014 - July 2015

Art & Design Foundation

September 2012 - July 2014

3 A-levels (grade A-B)

Graphic Design, Biology, Psychology

Avonbourne School

September 2007 - July 2012

GCSE - 12 GCSE's (grade A-C)

SKILLS

| Photoshop | • |
|---------------|---|
| Indesign | • |
| Illustrator | • |
| After Effects | • |
| Premier Pro | • |
| Muse | • |

Introduction

Hello my name is Tessa, I am a Graphic Designer based in Bournemouth with 2 years of design experience within the industry, I am bilingual and I speak fluent Cantonese and English. Sleek and clean with a little boldness is my approach to design. I take joy in editorial design as I like producing images and pairing it subtle typography with the occasional 'pop' of colour that captures the attention of the observer to keep looking for more. I have an interest for 'fashion' and I keep up to date with online fashion magazines and youtube videos. When I'm not arranging typefaces and picking out colour palettes you'll find me playing my guitar and scrolling through designers Instagram. I am drawn to exploring and gaining any form of insight I can get in the creative industry, I hope to broaden my knowledge of graphic design and learn through new experiences.

Design Experience

Edirect Digital Marketing Agency (Bournemouth)

February 2019 - September 2020 (1yr 6 Months)

- Branding and Logo Design
- App / Digital / Website Design
- Social Media Posts Design
- Marketing Proposals
- Print Design (Letterheads / Leaflets / Business Cards)
- Motion Graphics
- Mail Chimp Mailer Design

Parent Design Agency - Internship (Bournemouth)

October 2018 - November 2018

- Creating letterheads for property and housing companies
- Editorial Works
- Brochures and Leaflets for high-end hotels

A-list in-house designer (Bournemouth)

July 2018 - September 2018

- Worked independently as the only designer
- Created a website and updating their websites
- Flyers, posters, tickets and other promotional materials
- Admin work
- Curating a website on Wordpress for their new 'Print Business'

Other Work Experience

Retail assistant at New Look - temp (Bournemouth)

December 2017 - January 2018

Student ambassador at AUB

May 2017 - July 2017

Sales assistant at Primark (Bournemouth)

June 2017 - December 2017

Retail Assistant at Superdry (Bournemouth)

July 2016 - September 2016